Inventory of the Sheldon H. Harris Papers
Hoover Institution Archives
- International Citizens' Forum on War Crimes and Redress--symposium, Tokyo, 1999. (Folder 19: 5)
  Articles, clippings, letter, message, paper presented by Sheldon Harris, "Japanese Medical Atrocities in World War II: Unit 731 was not an Isolated Aberration," and printed matter
- GA Biennial Conference, Washington, D.C., 2000. (Folder 19: 6)
  Articles, program, and miscellany
- "The Living History Project: Remembering World War II in Asia,", 2000. (Folder 19: 7)
  Includes brochure and a paper presented by Sheldon Harris, "The American Cover-up of Japanese Human Biological Warfare Experiments, 1945-1948"
- International symposium on "Comfort Women," Shanghai, China, 2000. (Folder 19: 8)
  Clippings, letter, notes, printed matter, program, and report on the state of slave labor litigation in the United States courts against Japanese companies doing business in the United States
- "Biological Warfare: The Role of Public Discourse," Boston colloquium for Philosophy of Science, 2000/2001, Boston University (Box-folder 20: 1)
  Brochure, correspondence, message, papers by others, printed matter, program, and miscellany
- "Global Alliance for Preserving the History of World War II in Asia" conference, 2001. (Folder 20: 2)
  Clipping, newsletter, press kit, and printed matter
- "Fifty Years of Denial: Japan and Its Wartime Responsibilities," an international conference, and "Testimony to a Massacre," Rape of Nanking Redress Coalition, San Francisco, 2001. (Folder 20: 3)
  Brochure, printed matter, and program
- Zhejiang trip and field work, 2002. (Folder 20: 4)
  Brochure, correspondence, map, message, printed matter, and program. Includes 20 35mm slides of building and unidentified individuals
- Pin-fang meeting--Articles, 1989. (Folder 20: 5)
  Includes English translation of one of the articles. In Chinese
- Global Alliance for Preserving the History of World War II in Asia, 1998. (Folder 20: 6)
  Miscellany
- Maps of China, 2000 (Folder 20: 7)
- "Ethics of Biological Warfare Research," National Institute of Health (NIH) and Office for Protection from Research Risks (OPRR) seminar, California State University, Northridge, California, 1999. (Folder 20: 8)
  Announcement
- Simon Wiesenthal Center--Museum of Tolerance, 1999. (Folder 20: 9)
- Far East Society--China Tiffin Club meeting, San Francisco, 1998. (Folder 20: 10)
  Includes announcement of a speech by Sheldon Harris, "Japanese Medical Atrocities during World War II"
- The Millennium Commemoration of the Victims of World War IIin Asia meeting, Detroit Chinese Culture Service Center, Michigan, 1999. (Folder 20: 11)
  Acknowledgement
- "Residues of War: Class Actions by Former POWs in Japanese and Other Courts," speech by Sheldon Harris, Los Angeles? California, 1999. (Folder 20: 12)
- Till Barbnighausen, 1995. (Folder 20: 13)
  Correspondence
- Christie Maurice, 1999. (Folder 20: 14)
- Ignatius Ding, undated. (Folder 20: 15)
  Notes
- Edward Drea, 2000-2002. (Folder 20: 16-17)
- Correspondence and related materials
  - Duus, Peter, 1989 (Folder 20: 18)
  - Feinstein, Diane, 1999-2000 (Box-folder 21: 1)
  - Fitzgerald, Keith, 2002 (Folder 21: 2)
  - Franzblau, Michael J., 1995-2002 (Folder 21: 3)
  - Garrett, Ben, 1993-2000 (Folder 21: 4)
  - Geissler, Erhard, 1995-1999 (Folder 21: 5)
    Includes writings by Sheldon Harris
  - Gold, Hal, 1996-1999 (Folder 21: 6)
  - Hagers, Jos, 1989-1999 (Folder 21: 7)
  - Hugh-Jones, Martin, 1997-2002 (Folder 21: 8)
  - Hwa, Jesse, 2002 (Folder 21: 9)
  - Ichinose, Keiichiro, 1996-1997 (Folder 21: 10)
  - Jeljaszewicz, Janusz, 1995 (Folder 21: 11)
  - Kelly, Mark, 1998 (Folder 21: 12)
  - Kelly, Matt, 1996 (Folder 21: 13)
  - Kristof, Nicholas, 1995 (Folder 21: 14)
  - Leitenberg, Milton, 1997-1998 (Folder 21: 15)
  - McIntyre, Donald, 2002 (Box-folder 22: 1)
  - McLeod, Roy, 1999. (Folder 22: 2)
    Includes writing by Sheldon Harris
  - Moon, John Ellis van Courtland, 1997. (Folder 22: 3)
  - Mueller-Hill, Benno, 1996-1999 (Folder 22: 4)
  - Paxton, John, 1995 (Folder 22: 5)
  - Perlman, Richard, 1998 (Folder 22: 6)
  - Price, John, 1997-1999 (Folder 22: 7)
  - Pundeff, Marin, 1994-1995 (Folder 22: 8)
  - Rodvik, Robert S., 1994 (Folder 22: 9)
  - Roland, Charles G., 1995 (Folder 22: 10)
  - Shelokov, Alexis, 1997 (Folder 22: 11)
  - Shibata, Shingo, 1995-1997 (Folder 22: 12)
  - Sundstrom, Gerdt, 1995 (Folder 22: 13)
  - Tsuneishi, Kei'ichi, 1989 (Folder 22: 14)
  - Viallet, Serge, 1997-1999 (Folder 22: 15)
  - Wang, Xuan, 2002 (Folder 22: 16)
  - Wheelis, Mark, 1998 (Folder 22: 17)
  - Wikler, Daniel, 1995-1997 (Folder 22: 18)
  - Working, Russel, 1998-2001 (Folder 22: 19)
  - Zhao, Ling Shan, 1995-1999 (Folder 22: 20)
  - Miscellany, 1989-2002 (Folder 22: 21)
- Miscellany--Yasukuni Jinja, undated. (Folder 22: 22)
  Exhibition of treasures
- Miscellany, 1980-2002. (Box-folder 23: 1-5)
  Includes article, clippings, contract for publication and transfer of copyright of "The American Cover-up of Human Biological Warfare Experiments, 1945-1948," by Sheldon Harris, correspondence, memoranda, message, notes, press release, and printed matter
- Advocacy and Intelligence Index for Prisoners of War/Missing in Action (AIIPOWMIA), 1997. (Box-folder 24: 1)
  Articles about Unit 731, including one by Sheldon Harris, "Factories of Death: Japanese Biological Warfare, 1932-1945, and the American Cover-up," and review by Tien-wei Wu of various articles on the subject of Japanese biological warfare Unit 731
- California State University Emeritus and Retired Faculty Association (CSU-ERFA), 1998. (Folder 24: 2)
  Correspondence relating to Sheldon Harris' request for a grant for his research Project, Human Experiment Laboratory, Japanese Biological Warfare, 1932-1945, and the award of the grant
- Australia and New Zealand—Symposium, "Japan, U.S. and World War II: The Search for Justice," Tokyo, 1999. (Folder 24: 3)
  Correspondence, court documents, fact sheet, printed matter, and statement
- Trip to Australia, 1999. (Folder 24: 4)
  Printed matter and miscellany
- British Broadcasting Corporation (BBC), 1997-2001. (Folder 24: 5-6)
  Correspondence, including a letter to Sheldon Harris confirming his agreement to act as a consultant for a film on biological warfare. Includes printed matter
- Borden Institute, 1989-2000. (Folder 24: 7-8)
  Articles, including one by Sheldon Harris, "Biomedical Research and Atrocities in Prewar and World War II Japan;" brochure; clippings; correspondence; memoranda; and printed matter
- Factories of Death, by Sheldon Harris, 1999? (Box-folder 25: 1)
  Special introduction for the Chinese edition
- Discovery channel, 1998-2000. (Folder 25: 2)
  Correspondence, newsletter, printed matter, and miscellany
- Freedom of Information Act (FOIA), 1988-1995. (Folder 25: 3)
- Hiroshima Institute for Peace Education (HIPE), 1999. (Folder 25: 4)
  Correspondence, memoranda, printed matter, and miscellany. Includes article by Sheldon Harris, "The Present Problem of Peace Education in Japan"
- "Factories of Death," by Sheldon Harris--Japanese edition, 1998-2000. (Folder 25: 5)
  Articles by others, clippings, comments, correspondence, paper on special introduction and acknowledgements for the Japanese edition, note, printed matter, and resume of Sheldon Harris
- Japan National Institute of Health (NIH) lawsuit, 1999. (Folder 25: 6)
- Lawsuit in Japan and Unit 731 data, 1998-1999. (Folder 25: 7)
  Clippings, correspondence, and miscellany. In Japanese
- Marshall Cavendish Productions, Ltd., 1996-1997. (Folder 25: 8)
  Correspondence, invoice, message, and miscellany
- National Geographic, 2002. (Folder 25: 9)
  Correspondence relating to the publication of an article on weapons of mass destruction, with reference to Unit 731
- National Institute of Health (NIH) and Office for Protection from Research Risks (OPRR), 1999. (Folder 25: 10)
  Clippings, correspondence, purchase request, and miscellany
- New York fire fighters--Fire store order, 2001. (Folder 25: 11)
  Letter and miscellany
- Prometheus--Documentary on "Unholy Alliance: The Untold History of the United States and Unit 731,", 1999. (Folder 25: 12)
  Lists of interviews with survivors, witnesses, perpetrators, American military officials, authors, organizations, scholars, and miscellany
- Questia Media, Inc.(formerly TLG Media, Inc.), 2000. (Folder 25: 13)
  Agreement for participation in digital library project, list of signed authors, overview of copyright holder project, and publishing agreement
- Routledge, 1998-1999. (Folder 25: 14)
  Agreements and correspondence, including ones relating to the publication of "Factories of Death," and "Japanese Biological Warfare Experiments"
- Sheldon Harris--Retirement, 1963-1991. (Folder 25: 15)
  Comments and articles about him, and curriculum vitae
- Charles Stone and Japan's atom bomb project, 1997. (Folder 25: 16)
  Articles and correspondence
- Termite Art Productions, 1998-1999. (Folder 25: 17)
  Announcement; biography of J. V. Martin, producer; final script of "Unit 731: Nightmare in Manchuria;" and notes
- Tojo film and new nationalism, 1998. (Box-folder 26: 1)
  Clippings, message, and printed matter
- Tokyo deposition, 1998-1999. (Folder 26: 2)
  Clipping, correspondence, financial records, message, notes, printed matter, schedule, and miscellany
- Tokyo trial, 1995-1999. (Folder 26: 3)
  Article, clippings, correspondence, manifesto, message, notes, printed matter, and schedule for a press conference
- Tokyo lawyer's statement, 1998-1999. (Folder 26: 4)
  Includes clipping, correspondence, memoranda, note, and printed matter
- Wiesenthal Center, 2000. (Folder 26: 5)
  Article, clippings, correspondence, information kit, message, press release, printed matter, resume of Sheldon Harris and Barry A. Fisher, and miscellany. Includes 1 photographic print depicting Toshimi Mizobuchi with Rabbi Abraham Cooper, undated
- Hank Zeeman--Miscellany, 1980-1999. (Folder 26: 6)
  Includes articles, brief, certificate, interviews, letters, notes, paper on the history of claim for reparation for the Pacific war, printed matter, and miscellany. Also includes 5 photographic prints depicting Sheldon Harris, unidentified women, a house with a yard, and a dog, undated
- Miscellany, 1997-2000 (Folder 26: 7)
- Evidence of Guilt, by Minggan Qiu, 1999
- Pursuing the Japanese Auschwitz, by Shingo Takasugi, 1985 (Box-folder 27: 1)
- Printed matter relating to Commander Syoji Kondo's Isada testimony and script to manipulate troops on interrogations, 1998 (Folder 27: 2)
- Articles and clippings relating to germ warfare, 1990-1998, and Chinese statement on history of lawsuit, undated? (Folder 27: 3)
- Poster of Unit 731--Conference on Japan, California State University, Northridge, 2000 (Folder 27: 4)
- The Rape of Biological Warfare: Japanese Carnage in Asia during World War II, by James Yin, undated (Folder 27: 5)
- "War and Disease: What Unit 731 Brought,", 1997 (Folder 27: 6)
- Book on Unit 731 by a Japanese author, 1997. (Folder 27: 7)
  In Chinese
- Study of the Occupation of Northeast, vol. II, 1998 (Folder 27: 8)
- Shehuikexuezhanxian, 1995 (Folder 27: 9)
- 731, 1994. (Folder 27: 10)
  Journal
- Documents on great East Asian war found overseas, China, Korea, etc., vol. II, 1987 (Box-folder 28: 1)
- Japanese Military Presence in China, 1997 (Folder 28: 2)
- Bloody Rain, 1995 (Folder 28: 3)
- Organized Crime of Doctors, by Keiichi Tsuneishi, 1994 (Folder 28: 4)
- Writings by Shingo Shibata and others on Vietnam, Cuba, and about a new philosophy of human survival, 1968-1999 (Folder 28: 5)
- Article about atrocities committed on allied prisoners of war and postwar responsibilities, 1993 (Folder 28: 6)
- Paper on three ARL? Policy and the Japanese army's sexual crimes, by Kosahara Tokushi, conference at Chaugchun, 1998 (Folder 28: 7)
- "The Japanese Biological Warfare Study," John W. Powell, undated (Folder 28: 8)
- The Asian Holocaust 1931-1945: Hidden Holocaust in World War II by the Japanese Army--Photo exhibition of war atrocities committed by Japanese Army, 1998 (Folder 28: 9)
- Kyoto Museum for World Peace, 1995. (Folder 28: 10)
  Brochure
- Photo, 2000 (Folder 28: 11)
- Annual report of researchers, Hiroshima Institute for Peace Education, vol. 26, 1998 (Folder 28: 12)
- Miscellany, 1985-2001 (Box-folder 29: 1-9)
  Announcement by Japan of a program to compensate women victimized during World War II; article and outline by Sheldon Harris, "Biomedical Research and Atrocities in Prewar and World War II," 1998; clippings and printed matter relating to anthrax findings, biological weapons, and germ warfare; correspondence; Japan's denial of guilt for atrocities; Japan's production of banned chemical weapons; messages; notes; review by Ou Shuyi of Sheldon Harris, Factories of Death: Japanese Biological Warfare, 1932-1945, 2000; and United States defense of biological weapons and development of biological weapons by Iraq
- Clippings and printed matter relating to biological warfare, disclosure of World War II atrocities, and inquiry on radiation tests, 1989-2000 (Box-folder 30: 1)
- Japan news clippings--Unit 731, 1981-2000. (Folder 30: 2)
  Includes Japanese germ warfare and holocaust, protection offered by the United States to Emperor Hirohito and war criminals, and review of Sheldon Harris' book, Factories of Death, 1981-2000
- News clippings from China Daily, 1998-2000 (Folder 30: 3)
- Miscellany, 1989-2001. (Folder 30: 4)
  Clippings, messages, and printed matter mostly related to war crimes committed by Japan during World War II, radiation tests, and Japan's denial of responsibility
- Posters and publicity, 1994-1998. (Folder 30: 5)
  Announcements, brochure, letter of congratulations to Sheldon Harris for winning 1995 Scholarly Publication Award, and miscellany
- Videorecordings
  - VHS videocassettes
    - Inspector Morse, "Settling of the Sun," episode 2, undated
      (1 tape)
    - "Men behind the Sun?", undated
      - Original
        (2 tapes)
      - English version
    - Unit 731 report, Philip Short, British Broadcasting Corporation, introduction by Ms. Iwasa, undated (Box 30)
    - Unit 731, CH 13?, 2001
    - 60 Minutes and 20/20, undated (Box 31)
    - TV ASAHI, undated.
      NTSC broadcast standard (1 tape)
    - Unit 731, undated
    - Factories of Death--Interview with Sheldon Harris, NBC Dateline, 1995 August
    - "The Biological Unit 731," NHK, 1992, and "Unit 731: The Bacteriological Unit Is Still Alive," NTV, 1995
    - "A Glimpse of Reconciliation"--Unit 731, I and II, Alpha, Toronto, 1998
    - Unit 731, Acts 1-5: Stringout, 1999
    - "Unit 731 Is Alive," KBS documentary, undated; "Revived Spirit," part I, undated; and "Unfinished Judgement,", copied 1998
    - "Untold Story," NBC TV, 2000
    - "Life and Times Tonight,", 2000
    - "Protecting Human Subjects: Evolving Concern," "Balancing Society's Mandates," and "The Belmont Report,", 1986 (Box 32)
    - "SAIPAN," by Serge Vialett, undated
    - "Japanese War Crimes Teleconference," Simon Wiesenthal Center, undated
    - "Unit 731," Dateline NBC, undated
    - "Unit 731"--Germ warfare, 20/20 and 60 Minutes segments, undated
      (no sound) (1 tape)
    - "Nanking Massacre"--50th anniversary documents by Lang Yun, 1987
    - "Unit 731: The Biological Warfare Unit Is Still Alive,", undated
    - "The Forgotten Holocaust in Asia 8 Pacific: Japan's Germ Warfare in World War II,", 1998
    - Interview with Sheldon Harris, London, 1995
    - "Nightmare in Manchuria," History Channel, 1999
- Photocopies of 68 prints depicting unidentified men and women, army personnel, and buildings, sent to Sheldon Harris by Cecilia D'Gregory, undated (Box-folder 33: 1)
- 32 original 35mm slides, undated (Folder 33: 2)
- 25 photographic prints and 1 sheet containing photographs of 24 35mm slides, undated (Folder 33: 3)
- Correspondence and memorandum of agreement between Sheldon Harris and University of North Carolina Press regarding publication of "Japanese Biological Warfare Experiments in Manchuria, 1932-1945" (tentative title), 1989 (Folder 33: 4)
- Correspondence with Gordon Smith, Routledge, 1988-1994. (Folder 33: 5)
  Includes Sheldon Harris' writings and reviews, and related materials
- Pacific Circle Bulletin, 1998 (Folder 33: 6)
- Videorecordings
  - VHS videocassettes
    - "Do You Know Unit 731?", 1997
    - "Hirohito's Legacy,", 2001
    - "Horror in the East" (programs 1 and 2), 2000
    - "Comfort Women," 1994, and "Factory of Death: Unit 731,", 1995
    - "Bio-Chemical Weapons," Secrets of War, episode 30, narrated by Charlton Heston, undated
    - "Bloodsuckers,", 1998
    - Interview with Sheldon Harris, Los Angeles, channel 13, 2001
- 158 photographic prints depicting Sheldon Harris with possibly his family and unidentified individuals; prints of airport, buildings, conference room, gas station, market places, and public gatherings; and 37 35mm negatives of Manchuria and Death Camp photographs, 1984 (Box-folder 34: 1)
- 8 35mm slides and 36 35mm negatives depicting Harbin Camp, China, undated (Folder 34: 2)
- 26 35mm slides made from photos, undated (Folder 34: 3)
- 5 unidentified photographic prints, 1998, and 1 print depicting number of individuals gathered on the occasion of international symposium on Chinese "comfort women," Shanghai, China, 2000 (Folder 34: 4)
- Photocopies of 5 photographs and 1 miscellaneous printed paper, undated (Folder 34: 5)
- 28 photographic prints, including 26 depicting Unit 731facilities, undated; 1 depicting Shiro Ishii, undated; and 1 depicting youthful members of Unit 731, undated 57 35mm negatives relating to Unit 731
- 6 photographic prints depicting the germ bomb manufactured at Unit 731 in Pinfong, members of Unit 731, Shiro Ishii, doctor performing autopsy on a child, and members of the Unit, undated (Folder 34: 6)
- Drawing of Ping Fan (g) complex by 35-36 former Unit 731 members, given to Sheldon Harris by Koredo Sijoji (?) in Tokyo, 1996 (Folder 34: 7)
- 5 photocopies of photographs depicting punishment and torture bench, skulls, and bones with fractures unearthed in Tokyo, undated
- 1 photographic print depicting a disfigured face of a lady, returned to Sheldon Harris with a note attached to it, 2000
- 17 unidentified photocopies of photographs including 1 depicting one corner area where artifacts were located, undated
- Photocopies of 18 photographs depicting personnel, facilities and operations of Unit 731, undated (Folder 34: 8)
- Routledge marketing plan for the book, Factories of Death, and printed matter, 2001-2002 (Folder 34: 9)
- Correspondence with Gordon Smith detailing his comments about the book, Factories of Death? and review of the manuscript by R. John Pritchard, 1992 (Folder 34: 10)
- Book reviews, 1989-2001. (Folder 34: 11)
  Includes brochures, bulletins, correspondence, journal, list of books for public and high school libraries, newsletter, and printed matter
- Miscellany, 1995-1998. (Box-folder 35: 1)
  List of revisions, letters, memoranda, newsletter, notes, photocopies of photographs, preface to the paperback edition of Factories of Death, and printed matter
- Reviews of Sheldon Harris, Factories of Death, 1993-1999. (Folder 35: 2)
  Includes brochure, clippings, and newsletter
- 14 35mm slides, undated; 3 3.5-inch computer disks containing information about China trip, 1998; and lists of JPEG file names for the 35mm slides (Folder 35: 3)
- The "Rotten Leg" Victims of Zeijang: Photographs and Testimonies, collected, 2002. (Folder 35: 4)
  Includes 24 digital prints, 38 35mm slides, and 1 digital CD of China victims
- Sound recording
  - Compact sound cassettes
    - Plutonium, undated
    - KNBR interview, undated
    - San Francisco, 1995
    - KSFR roundtable with Matt Kelly Ireland, 1996
      (2 compact sound cassettes)
    - Swedish radio broadcast, 1997
    - "Japan and Germ Warfare in World War II," CBC early edition, 1998
    - Rafe(?) Mair interview, 1998
    - Savage, 1998
- "The Dugway Documents: The Japanese Biological Warfare Program," vol. I, Anthrax, by Martin Furmanski and Sheldon H. Harris, 2001.
  1 compact disc
- The Report of "Q,", undated. (Box-folder 36: 1-4)
  Plague
- The Report of "A,", undated (Box-folder 37: 1-4)
- Factories of Death (Box 38)
  - Special introduction for Chinese edition, undated (Folder 38: 1)
  - Paperback edition, undated (Folder 38: 2)
  - Miscellany, 1991-2001 and undated (Folder 38: 3)
    Guidelines for Routledge authors, invoice, and notes
  - 4 3.5-inch computer disks for revisions, 1-3 and part III, and 1 compact disc for back up, undated
- Preparation of a proposal for a grant from the National Endowment for the Humanities, undated. Includes a memorandum to the Department of Humanities and Social Sciences, California State University, Northridge, from Mark Lipschutz, 2000 (Folder 38: 4)
- Glanders--The Report of "G,", undated (Folder 38: 5-8)
- Hopes for a Network: Admit the Fact of Germ Warfare and Apologize to Victims to Compensate, undated. (Folder 38: 9)
  Newsletter
- Factories of Death--Draft, undated and second edition, 2001. (Box-folder 39: 1-8)
- Factories of Death, undated. (Box-folder 40: 1-9)
  Bibliography, draft chapters, notes, and copies of marked proof pages relating to queries
- Milberg Weiss Bershad Hynesb 8 Lerach LLP (MWBHL), 2000. (Box-folder 41: 1-2)
  Case numbers and filing dates, clippings, conference papers, correspondences, court documents, invoices, list of companies and their affiliates doing business in California who owe compensation to victims of slave labor, memoranda, printed matter regarding slave/forced labor claims and newspaper coverage of litigation, and notes. Includes a paper by Sheldon Harris, "Japanese Medical Atrocities in World War II: Unit 731 Was Not an Isolated Aberration," presented at the International Citizens Forum on War Crimes 8 Redress, Tokyo, 1999, and 1 photographic print depicting unidentified individuals, undated
- Draft chapters of Factories of Death, undated (Folder 41: 3-6)
- Chinese holocaust, 1999-2000. (Box-folder 42: 1-2)
  War and the Rights of Individuals: Renaissance of Individual Compensation, edited by Hisakazu Fujita, Isomi Suzuki, and Kantaro Nagano; court documents; expense report; letters, including one about Sheldon Harris' appointment as a consultant by Milberg Weiss Bershad Hynes 8 Lerach LLP; memoranda; notes; printed matter; and miscellany
- Chinese holocaust litigation, 1998. (Folder 42: 3)
  Court documents
- Howard Rubinstein, 2001. (Folder 42: 4)
  Article on treaty of peace with Japan, undated; expense report and summary of corporate card account; letters, including to Florida Bar Association relating to Rubinstein's failure to pay Sheldon Harris for his consulting services; list of Florida Bar Legal Division branch offices and staff; notes; and miscellany
- U.S. litigation, 2002. (Folder 42: 5)
  Preliminary working draft of statement of jurisdiction
- Slave Labor Project, 2002. (Folder 42: 6)
  Expense sheet
- Japan trial, 2000-2001. (Folder 42: 7)
  Testimony
- Review of Stephen Endicott and Edward Hagerman, The United States and Biological Warfare: Secrets from the Early Cold War and Korea, by Sheldon Harris for the Journal of American History, 1999. (Box-folder 43: 1)
  Includes letter, notes, printed copy, and miscellany
- Review of Igor V. Domaradskij's manuscript, "Troublemaker," for Central European University Press (CEU), 2000. (Folder 43: 2)
  Includes correspondence, draft, and information sheet
- Acres of Skin: Human Experiments at Holmesburg Prison, by Allen M. Hornblum, 1998. (Folder 43: 3)
  Draft writings, information packet with dates the author would be available for interview, and letter requesting Sheldon Harris to endorse the project
- "Three Years with the Emperor," by Sigfreid A. Schreiner, 1941-1990. (Box-folder 44: 1)